<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RidzApp</string>

    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_michael">michael</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="michael_story">Michael was born on October 10, 1974. After his father, Aldo Burrows, deserted the family before his birth, Michael took up his mother\'s maiden name as his own surname in order to start a new life because she told him that his father was an alcoholic and drug user (which was later proved untrue). (1x4) When Michael was 11 and Lincoln was 15, their mother (then age 31) supposedly died of a brain aneurysm brought on by a brain tumor (she is later found to be alive), though it was initially thought to be liver cancer. Lincoln, his older brother, became his guardian and tried his best to take care of him. Having lost both their parents, Lincoln descended into a deep life of crime. Howeve, Lincoln worked hard to prevent Michael from taking his own path and suffering the same fate. This became one of Michael\'s reasons for hatching an escape plan to help his brother.(1x5, 1x16)

Following the death of his mother, he and Lincoln moved in with the family of Lincoln\'s friend, Veronica Donovan. This situation was short-lived. Afterwards, Michael and Lincoln both traveled in and out of different foster home situations. Though they were usually kept together, there were periods of time when circumstances required them to be placed separately. One such instance occurred when Lincoln did a six-month sentence stretch in juvenile hall on an assault charge when Michael was 11. Michael was placed with an abusive foster father in the Pershing section of Chicago; who routinely locked Michael and his other charges in a small storage shed. Six months into Michael\'s stay, his foster father was found dead in his home, a victim of a violent attack: killed by Aldo, where he rescued Michael. For better or worse, young Michael repressed all memory of what had occurred and was not able to help police in their investigation. To this day, the murder investigation itself remains unsolved.

When Michael would wake up in the mornings not knowing where his brother was, there would be an origami crane next to his bed, a sign his brother was watching out for him.

In Morton East High School in Cicero, Illinois, Michael took an elective survey class in Arts and Crafts, which had a large section devoted to the Japanese art of origami. He was immediately drawn to the precision and patience that the practice required. This fascinated him to an extent that he began constructing a number of cranes out of any material he could find. Michael was so fond of his habit that his practice of making paper cranes carried over and continued into his adulthood.

Michael was a gifted student, and finished his secondary education at Morton East High School with an impeccable record; He graduated Magna Cum Laude with a Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Degree and a Master of Science (M.S.) Degree in Civil Engineering from Loyola University in Chicago. After which, he went on to become successful as a structural engineer at the prestigious architecture firm of \'Middleton, Maxwell and Schaum in downtown Chicago. Michael says that he has no religion, as he had no time to think about it before getting into jail (1x1), although in truth he was raised Catholic, as he goes to confession in New Mexico and tells the priest it is his first confession in a long time. (2x11)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sara">sara</string>
    <string name="sara_story">Raised in Chicago, Sara Tancredi\'s ambitions to be a doctor began when she was very young. While at Northwestern University, she was introduced to the works of Mahatma Gandhi and decided to become a humanitarian, which later influenced her decision to work at Fox River State Penitentiary. She has also won at least one Humanitarians Award. (1x1) Another factor which contributed to her occupational choice was her past morphine addiction. (1x16) At 29 years old, Dr. Sara Tancredi was one of the few doctors working at Fox River. Her chosen occupation became a constant source of stress for her father. Sara is the only child of the Governor of Illinois, Frank Tancredi. Due to her father\'s hectic political career and vastly differing beliefs, Sara did not have a close relationship with her father. Her mother is already dead. (2x7)

</string>
    <string name="button1">New Button</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

</resources>
